

AMAN SHARMA

EMAIL ID – DIXIT28.AMAN@GMAIL.COM CONTACT NO. -9873357261

OBJECTIVE

I am looking for the challenging job where I can utilize my talent and my knowledge, I want to learn from the organization.

SKILLS

Autocad 2d , Revit Architecture, Stadd PRO v8i, QGIS, ArcGIS , Erdas Imagine MS Office.

EXPERIENCE

SGS InfoTech Pvt Ltd from April 2013 to May 2016 as Executive.

Quantum Asia Pvt Ltd. From June 2016 to May 2019 as Executive.

Presently working in Isotech consultants (Design Support Team) From June 2019 to till date as Cad/Revit Technician.

EDUCATION

MANGLAM SCHOOL OF MANAGEMENT & TECHNOLOGY- DELHI – 2013-2016

Bachelor of Engineering (Civil Engineering)

PDM POLYTECHNIC COLLEGE – BAHADURGARH- 2010-2013

Diploma in Civil Engineering

SUMMARY

Highly Motivated Architectural Technician & GIS with 5 years' Experience in Architectural & GIS Industry. Good Drafting Skill & Knowledge of CAD 2d & Revit in various projects such as Building Commercial, Residential, and Industrial Buildings.

PROJECT INVOLVED

Auto Cad & Revit Architectural Drawing

Cadastral(Khasra) Projects (MP, UP, Bihar and HP)

UK Maps -London, Land Use

NIC Digitization & Quality Check

Geo Referencing of Carto set data

CAD ARCHITECT

Responsible in various task such as projection of working drawing (Floor Plan, Section, Elevation, Interior details etc.)

GIS

Responsible in various task such as Cadastral Mapping, UK Maps –London, NIC Digitization & Quality Check ,Geo Referencing of Carto set data etc.

REVIT

Responsible in various task such as projection of working drawing (Floor Plan, Section, Elevation, Interior details etc.)

Project Involved

Bagmane Capital Infra - This is the Basic Modeling on behalf of the CAD drawings provided By Client.

Cann Tech Engg. - This is the Hospital Basic Design Modeling on behalf of the CAD drawings provided By Client.

STRENGTHS:

Teamwork and Leadership HardWorking Quick learner Self-Motivated Positive Attitude

COMMUNICATION

Hindi & English (Verbal & Written)

HOBBIES

Travelling Music Sports Socializing

PERSONAL PROFILE

Father, s Name RP Sharma

Date of birth 28/03/1992

Address Street no & name -7, Chottu Ram Park

City - Bahadurgarh, State - Haryana, Pin-12450.

Sex Male Marital Single

Nationality Indian

Date:

Place: (AMAN SHARMA)